perfectgame.org 2019-07-07

# Perfect Game USA - World's Largest Baseball Scouting Service

Last Updated: May 24, 2019

This updated Privacy Policy reflects Perfect Game, Inc. commitments and obligations under the EU’s new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Your privacy is important to us, so the goal of this policy is to be transparent about what information PG collects, uses, and shares.

This policy explains your rights with regards to that information. It also explains how to access and update your information, and how you can object to its use.

When we refer to “PG”, “we”, or “us”, we mean the Perfect Game, Inc., A US Corporation based in Iowa that acts as the controller or processor of your information.

Any personally identifying information you provide is voluntary. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [privacy@perfectgame.org](mailto:privacy@perfectgame.org). 

What information we collect and how we use it 

How we share information

How we store, secure, and transfer information

Your data rights and choices

Advertising

List of data sub-processors

Other 

When we make changes to our Privacy Policy, we will revise the date at the top of this page.

When you sign up, create a profile, set your preferences, or pay for your subscription, PG collects the information you voluntarily provide in communications and transactions with Perfect Game Inc. such as your name, username, password, email, credit card information, and any profile pictures, avatars, or digital images you choose to upload. 

We use this information to correctly identify you, communicate with you, and provide you with customer support. We also use this contact information for accounting and administrative purposes, for transactional emails and to notify you about new features, releases and blog posts. 

We collect information about the type of device you use to access PG, as well as your device settings, operating system, browser information, connection type, IP address, and the URLs of referring pages. Additionally, we log the date and time you access our services, as well as any error or crash data.

We use device and location information to help us optimize your display and performance, understand user demographics, and improve overall user experience. Your log data helps us troubleshoot errors, analyze performance, resolve reliability issues, perform security audits, and investigate potential service fraud or abuse.

This data is generated automatically, when you visit PG. It provides us with information about how you browse our website and use our app. That includes the links you click, the search terms you use, and the features you access.

We use this metadata to help us understand how our users work, and what they find most valuable at PG. We also use this information to measure the efficiency of our product, enhance our services and guide our future development.

PG and our third-party advertising and analytics partners use cookies and similar technologies for tracking across different devices, websites and online services.

We use this information both for secure authentication and for the maintenance of your active sessions. Our third-party partners use cookies for the purposes of marketing, ad targeting, and performance analytics.

Whenever you or your account owner links to a third-party service, PG is authorized to connect and transfer information as specified by our agreement with that linked service.

We use this information to authenticate, connect, or link your third-party accounts to PG. However, we do not receive or store passwords for any of these third-party services.

To understand what data may be shared with PG when you enable these integrations, please check the settings, permissions and privacy policies of these third-party services.

Our web site’s team or player profile pages; subscriptions for scouting, subscriptions for videos or sales of other goods and services uses fill in forms that may ask users to voluntarily provide us with contact information (such as name, e-mail and postal addresses), payment processing (such as bank or credit/debit card numbers), and demographic information (such as city, state, zip code and age). 

Contact information from team or player profile pages; subscriptions for services, subscriptions for videos or sales of other goods and services forms are used to contact customers, when necessary. This data is necessary for the processing of, and future identification of, teams, players, subscriptions and sales of other goods and confirmation of mailing addresses, and is used solely for those purposes. 

Payment Information is never given or sold to third parties for any purpose, except to PG and to third-party service providers acting on its behalf. 

Personally Identifiable Information (PII) may be collected in order to process payments. This information is never made public nor given or sold to third parties for any purpose, except to PG and to third-party service providers acting on its behalf or the purpose it was given. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This data is necessary for promotion of a player or team and for statistical purposes and is used solely for that purpose. This non PII information is publicly available to visitors to our site. 

PG may disclose your personal information among its affiliated businesses and with third-party service providers acting on PG's behalf. 

The personal information you provide may be transmitted, used, stored and otherwise processed outside of the country where you submitted that information, including jurisdictions that may not have data privacy laws that provide equivalent protection to such laws in your home country. 

PG uses encryption and authentication tools to protect your personal information. The information you may provide through our Web site is secured using industry-standard security matters to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as perfect security on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to ensure the safety of your personal information. In addition, our employees are instructed that such information is to be used only in accordance with the principles of this Privacy Policy and the laws applicable to each specific business. Employees who misuse customer information are subject to disciplinary action. 

This site may contain links to other sites not monitored by or controlled by PG. Neither PG shall be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such non-controlled linked web sites. 

If PG engages in a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, dissolution, sale of company assets, financing, public offering of securities, or due diligence and other steps in contemplation and negotiation of such activities, we may share or transfer information that we collect under this privacy policy, subject to standard confidentiality agreements.

How we store, secure, and transfer information

PG takes data security very seriously and implements the industry’s best practices and policies. We take all reasonable measures to protect your information, and to prevent any kind of unauthorized access, misuse, loss, or disclosure.

While no system is infallible, we strive to keep our systems secure and constantly updated.

PG may also retain certain information for as long as necessary in order to support business operations, or as required by law.

PG collects information internationally and uses hosting and cloud computing infrastructure located primarily in the United States to transfer, process and store information. In order to provide you with our service, we may also transfer your data to third-party services. Please refer to the List of data sub-processors for more information about why we use those third-party services, and where they are located.

The following is a summary of choices you can make to exercise your data rights:

You have the right to be forgotten which means that, at any time, you can request that PG permanently delete all applicable data records, including your profile information, along with any user-created content. In some cases, we may need to retain partial information to fulfil our legal responsibilities.

You have the right, at any time, to request and receive the information that you have provided to PG. We will provide you with your information, in a machine-readable format, so that you can make use of it in other contexts, or with other service providers.

PG services are not directed at children. Furthermore, we do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under 16 years of age, unless consent is given or authorized by the holder of parental responsibility over the child. If we become aware that someone under 16 has provided us with personal details, we will take steps to delete such information. If you become aware that a child has unlawfully or unwittingly provided us with personal data, please contact our Support team.

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in www.perfectgame.org. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. 

PG Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party sites for more detailed information. 

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions. 

Even if you have previously consented to our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, you have the right, at any time, to change your mind and object to the collection, use, and processing of your personal information. Additionally, you are under no contractual obligation to continue to provide any information to PG. However, we require certain information in order to provide you with our services. Therefore, if you disagree with the terms of this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Service, you should stop using PG, and contact us so that we may delete your information.

PG may modify this Agreement from time to time and such modification shall be effective upon posting by PG on the Site. You agree to be bound to any changes to this Agreement when you use the Site Services after any such modification is posted. It is therefore important that you review this Agreement regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes. 

PG, reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to reject, refuse to post or remove any posting (including private messages) by you, or to restrict, suspend, or terminate your access to all or any part of the Site Services at any time, for any or no reason, with or without prior notice, and without liability. PG, expressly reserves the right to remove your profile and/or restrict, suspend, or terminate your access to any part of Site Services if PG determines, in its sole discretion, that you pose a threat to PG and/or its Users.

If you have any questions about PG Privacy Policy or want to make a request with regard to your information, please contact our Data Protection Officer at [privacy@perfectgame.org](mailto:privacy@perfectgame.org).
